This world is rotten.
Criminals keep increasing, and justice is powerless.
What is this? "Death Note"... a notebook of death?
"The human whose name is written in this note shall die."
Ridiculous. It must be someone's prank.
But... what if it were real?
"The writer must have the subject's face in mind when writing the name, or it will not take effect."
In other words, people with the same name won't die by mistake.
"If the cause of death is not specified, the subject will die of a heart attack."
A heart attack... meaning it would appear to be a natural death.
"When writing the details of death, it must be done within six minutes and forty seconds."
Should I test it... No, there's no way someone would actually die.
However, if this notebook is real,
I can change the world.
I will judge criminals and create a new world.
I will... carry out justice with this notebook.
No one will be able to stop me.
I will become the god of the new world.
Using this Death Note,
I will build the ideal world.