Criminals around the world are dying one after another from heart attacks.
On the internet, it seems they are calling
the one causing this phenomenon "Kira."
At the request of the ICPO, I have been assigned to investigate this case.
I am L. If someone is judging criminals,
then that person is also a criminal.
Kira, I want to ask you.
Is what you are doing truly justice?
This man... Lind L. Tailor?
There is no way L would appear in public.
I will find you without fail.
I will prove that I am justice.
I'll take the bait.
If I write this man's name, I'll learn L's true identity.
Tailor has died. It was a heart attack.
So Kira really can kill.
However, that was not me just now.
Kira, that just now confirmed it.
You have the ability to kill people.
What... It was a trap!
That man was a stand-in for L!
Furthermore, I have obtained crucial information.
Kira is in the Kanto region.
This broadcast was limited to the Kanto region.
The fact that you reacted means you are there.
He got me... I fell completely into L's trap.
But I will not give up.
Whoever L may be, I will eliminate him.
L, in this battle, I will be the one who wins in the end.
Kira versus L. An unprecedented battle of wits
between two geniuses has begun.
Which side holds justice?
No one can say for certain.