You're an interesting human, Light Yagami.
Who are you?
How do you know my name?
I am the shinigami Ryuk.
I am the original owner of that Death Note.
A shinigami... I never imagined they actually existed.
I want to propose a deal to you.
The deal for the shinigami eyes.
If you possess the shinigami eyes, just by looking at
a human's face, you can see their name and remaining lifespan.
If you can see their name, you can write it in the notebook immediately.
Convenient, wouldn't you say?
But there is a price.
In exchange for obtaining the shinigami eyes, you lose half your remaining lifespan.
Half my lifespan?
I cannot agree to such a deal.
I must reign as the god of the new world for a long time.
I cannot afford to shorten my lifespan.
I see. Well, let me know whenever you change your mind.
I want to ask you one thing. Is it true that a human
who uses the Death Note can go to neither heaven nor hell after death?
Yes, that is true.
A human who has touched the Death Note returns to nothingness.
I see... Even so, I do not mind.
My resolve will not change.
Even if I cannot go to heaven,
purifying this rotten world is my mission.
Ryuk, all you need to do is watch.
Watch how I build the new world.
Interesting. Humans really are fascinating.