Let's go to Grizzly's bar.
Good evening. Welcome!
Grizzly, your shop is so cool!
Thanks. I built it myself.
What would you like to drink?
What do you recommend?
Today's recommendation is honey milk.
Honey! That sounds good. I'll have that please.
Grizzly, how long have you been running the bar?
Since three years ago.
What is your dream?
I want to have a bigger shop.
That's a wonderful dream.
Unlike Polar Bear's cafe, this is a nighttime shop.
The nighttime atmosphere is nice too, isn't it?
Do many customers come?
Weekends are busy. Weekdays are quiet.
Let's both do our best!
It's getting late. I should head home soon.
Please come again. Good night!