In the year 2015 A.D., humanity was still recovering from the catastrophe known as "Second Impact."
Welcome to the special agency NERV, Shinji Ikari.
Target confirmed. Massive object detected approaching Tokyo-3.
An Angel, as I thought. The first one in fifteen years.
Conventional weapons from the UN forces have absolutely no effect against the Angel.
As long as it's deploying an AT Field, conventional weapons are powerless.
Commander Ikari, requesting authorization to use an N2 mine.
Activate Evangelion Unit-01. Has the pilot arrived?
I'm supposed to... ride this thing? This robot?
An Eva is not a robot. It is the multipurpose humanoid decisive weapon — the artificial human, Evangelion.
Get in. Otherwise, go home.
Father... you called me here just for this?
The synchronization rate is abnormally high. These readings are unprecedented for an initial connection.
Eva Unit-01, launch preparations complete. Release all restraints.
Connected to launch catapult. Initiating launch sequence.
Evangelion Unit-01, launch!
The Angel is attacking! Take evasive action!
Unit-01 is out of control! The pilot's vital signs are dropping rapidly!
Unit-01 has... gone berserk? Is this the Eva's true form?
Angel silence confirmed. Pattern blue, annihilated. Primary operation, complete.