I'm the transfer student, Shinji Ikari. Nice to meet you.
That guy is the Eva pilot? A normal kid like him?
Toji, your sister got hurt in that battle, right? It's his fault.
Why are you hitting me? It's not like I wanted to pilot the Eva.
Emergency situation. The Fourth Angel is approaching from the Hakone Mountain area. All personnel, assume Level One battle stations.
Shinji Ikari, report to NERV headquarters immediately. Repeat, report immediately.
Eva Unit-01, commencing activation sequence. The pilot's mental state is unstable.
It doesn't matter. Send him out. There is no other means to defeat the Angel.
Distance to target, 1200 meters. Now within firing range.
Suppress it with the pallet rifle. Neutralizing the AT Field is top priority.
Unable to neutralize the AT Field! Insufficient power output!
The power cable has been severed! Switching to internal battery. Four minutes and thirty-two seconds until operational limit.
Ikari, stay calm. You can do this. Focus.
Use the progressive knife! Force it into close combat!
Angel core confirmed. Destroying that red sphere should defeat it.
Thirty seconds until operational limit. Hurry, Ikari!
Angel, activity ceased. Core destruction confirmed. Operation complete.
That was incredible, Ikari. You really defeated the Angel.
Nobody ever calls. Even if I weren't here, nobody would care.
Ikari, you're always alone, aren't you? You look kind of lonely.