Nice to meet you. I'm Shota. Pleased to meet you all.
Um, I'm from Tokyo, and right now I'm working as an office worker.
I'm Misaki. I came from Osaka.
Oh, you're from Osaka. That's cool.
Yeah, but I'm already used to life in Tokyo.
I'm Kenta. I'm a college student studying architecture.
Architecture, huh. That's cool. What do you want to be in the future?
My dream is to design my own house.
Oh, I'm Mai. I work as a model.
Wow! Do you appear on TV and stuff?
No, just magazines so far. But I'm working hard at it.
I'm Daiki. I love surfing, and I used to live in Shonan.
Surfing! That's so nice. I want to try it too.
Then I'll teach you sometime. Let's all go together.
This house is really spacious, isn't it? The kitchen is big too.
It really is. We can all cook together. Sounds fun.
Well then, looking forward to living with everyone.
Same here! I hope we have a good time together.
I'm kind of nervous, but it's exciting, right?
Yeah, it's definitely going to be fun. Let's do our best together.