Who's going to make dinner tonight?
Well, should I make it? Is curry okay?
Curry! Sounds great. Can you actually cook, Daiki?
I'm decent, I guess. I lived alone for a long time.
Then I'll help out. I'll cut the vegetables.
Thanks, Misaki. Can you do the onions and carrots?
This knife cuts really well. I need to be careful.
Hey, Shota. Could you cook the rice?
Sure. How many cups should I cook?
There are six of us, so about four cups, I think.
Wow, it smells so good. I'm getting hungry.
Just wait a little longer. About ten more minutes.
Then, should we set the table?
I'll line up the chopsticks and plates here.
It's done! Everyone, come over. Let's eat.
Let's eat. Mmm, it's delicious! You're amazing, Daiki.
It really is. It's like restaurant quality.
No, no, it's nothing special. But I'm glad you like it.
Eating together really does make food taste better, doesn't it?
I'll cook tomorrow. What would you all like?