Hey, what are everyone's dreams for the future?
I want to open my own cafe someday.
Wait, a cafe? Do you like coffee, Daiki?
Yeah, I love it. I want to do it near the ocean.
That's great. Coffee after surfing would be the best.
What about you, Misaki? How's your job going?
I'm working at an IT company now, but I really want to become a writer.
Really? What do you want to write about?
Travel. I want to write articles while traveling around the world.
That's cool. But would you quit your current job?
I haven't decided yet. It's a little scary, you know?
I get it. Quitting a stable job takes a lot of courage.
Kenta, you said you want to be an architect, right?
Yeah. But lately I've been interested in eco-friendly buildings.
What about you, Mai? What do you want to do in the future?
I like modeling, but someday I want to create my own brand.
Clothes? Or accessories?
Clothes. Simple but stylish ones.
It's nice that everyone has dreams. I'm rooting for you all.
Thanks. I hope living here becomes some kind of turning point for us.