Hey, can I talk to you about something today?
Of course. What's going on?
Actually, I haven't been getting along with my parents lately.
I see. Did something happen?
They're against my modeling career. They keep telling me to get a stable job.
Parents do worry, don't they? But I understand how you feel, Mai.
Thanks. It means a lot to have someone who understands.
Actually, I've been struggling with family stuff too.
Wait, really? You too, Daiki?
Yeah. My father is a strict person. He barely ever praised me growing up.
That must be tough. But I think you're a really kind person, Daiki.
I've been thinking lately, isn't it hard to like yourself?
Yeah, it is. But I think we can change little by little.
Maybe it was a good idea to come to this house. Because we can have talks like this.
We don't usually get to have conversations like these, do we?
I realized that everyone has their own worries.
But having a place where you can talk about them is important, right?
Yeah. I don't want to keep everything bottled up inside.
If anything comes up, tell me anytime. I'll listen.
Thank you. Really, thank you.