Hey, Nishikata. What are you doing?
N-Nothing! I'm not doing anything.
Is there something written on that eraser?
Huh? There's nothing written! Don't look!
The more you hide it, the more curious I get, you know.
I'm not hiding anything! It's just a regular eraser.
Then you wouldn't mind showing me, right?
N-No way! Absolutely not!
Did you know that if you write the name
of the person you like on an eraser, they'll like you back?
I-I don't believe in stuff like that!
Your face is turning red, Nishikata.
It's not red! It's just hot in here!
It's not that hot today, though.
Geez... Takagi-san, you're always teasing me.
I'm not teasing you. You're just funny, Nishikata.
The teacher's coming. You should put that eraser away, don't you think?
Oh no! Where did I put it?
Here, you dropped it.
Oh, th-thanks... You didn't look at it, right?
Hmm, who knows?