Today's class is calligraphy. Please be quiet.
Nishikata, are you good at calligraphy?
I'm average, I guess. What about you, Takagi-san?
Me? Hmm, I'm okay, I suppose.
Then, want to have a contest? To see who writes better.
Sure. What does the loser have to do?
The loser has to... do one thing the winner says!
Sounds fun. Okay, let's do it.
All right, I'm definitely going to win!
The subject will be "Friend." Please look at my example.
I don't have enough ink. I'll put on a bit more.
Nishikata, you're holding the brush a little wrong.
Huh, really? What's wrong with it?
You should hold it a bit higher. Like this.
Oh, you're right. Thanks.
Done! How is it? I think I wrote it pretty well.
Yeah, it's good. But mine might be better.
Whoa... it really is good.
So, I win then. You'll do one thing I ask, okay?
What are you planning to ask... That's scary.