Nishikata, have you ever had canned coffee?
Of course I have. I've had it lots of times.
Oh really? Then what about black coffee?
Black? I can drink black coffee too... probably.
"Probably"? Have you really had it before?
I have! I can appreciate grown-up flavors!
Then let's go buy some. There's a vending machine.
Huh... right now? I mean, sure, that's fine.
Here, a black coffee. Here you go.
Thanks. Okay, let's drink them together.
Ready, set...
B-Bitter...! But, it's fine. I can drink it.
You don't have to force yourself. Your face looks terrible.
I'm not forcing anything! Something like this is nothing!
I actually like black coffee quite a bit.
No way... You actually think it tastes good?
Yeah. Once you get used to it, it becomes delicious.
Coffee with sugar is definitely better, though.
Well, you don't have to force yourself to drink black, you know.
Damn, I feel like I lost to Takagi-san again.