Today's class duty is Nishikata-kun and Takagi-san.
Huh, class duty with Takagi-san? Seriously...
Let's work well together, Nishikata.
First we need to erase the blackboard. Can you hand me the chalk?
Here you go. Do you need white or red?
White is fine. Thanks.
What should we write in the class log? Did anything happen today?
I guess Tanaka fell asleep during third period.
If you write that, Tanaka's going to be mad at you.
Then let's just write "Nothing noteworthy happened today."
Nishikata, your handwriting is neat. That's unexpected.
What do you mean "unexpected"?!
I'm complimenting you. Just take it gracefully.
Next we need to water the flowers. Where's the watering can?
It's in the locker. I'll go get it.
Thanks. You're kind, Nishikata.
I-It's nothing special. We're on class duty, after all.
Doing duty together once in a while is nice, isn't it?
Well... yeah. It's not bad, I guess.
It'd be nice if we could be on class duty together again.